marketingwithyou.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy - MarketingWithYou.com | Alex Jeffreys

How We Protect Your Privacy

This website privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our website (http://www.marketingwithyou.com), you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this website privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this website privacy policy.

Minors

We do not provide services or sell products to children. However, we may sell products to adults for use by children. Regardless of the intended end user of our products, only adults should purchase anything from our website. If a product we offer is legal only for adults to use or possess, no adult should purchase the product for illegal use or possession by a minor.

If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission, active involvement, and supervision of an adult parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information. 

This Policy Is Part Of Our Terms And Conditions Of Use

Our website privacy policy is a part of, and subject to, our website’s terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions on our website.

The type of information we collect from you and interest-based advertising.

Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer’s operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you.

And like many other websites, we may use cookies, click redirects, pixel tags, container tags, and similar technologies. In plain English, this means information that our website’s server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website and to customize our website content for you as an individual. 

If you are using one of the common Internet Web browsers, you can set up your browser to either (a) let you know when you are being tracked by us or to (b) deny us tracking access to your computer or electronic mobile device. The manufacturer of the browser you use has instructions on how to modify tracking settings. You may find these instructions in the “Help” section of your browser or by contacting the browser’s manufacturer.

If you download or use mobile software applications (“Mobile Apps”) from our website, we may know your location. In addition, your smart phone, computer tablet, or other electronic device using our Mobile Apps may provide us information about the device, including its unique identifier, make and model, operating system, mobile network carrier, and your telephone number.

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by sending to us via email. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website’s services and features.

Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders, and/or third party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number, and other information related to the transaction.

What We Do With Your Information

We use your information to operate our website’s business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, new products and services, special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website’s terms and conditions.

If you download or use Mobile Apps from our website, the information we learn about you may be used by us to give you personalized content based upon your location and other data you share. If you do not want to share your location via Mobile Apps, check the instruction manual for your electronic device or contact your device’s manufacturer to see if you can turn off the locator feature.

As a general rule, we will not give your data to third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs.

We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability.

Some government intelligence agencies have the technological ability to access data from our website without our cooperation, knowledge, or consent. Even if we were to learn of such access, we may not be able to tell you because of national security laws. Please take this risk into account before supplying information to us or any other website owner.

Although we do not disclose individually identifiable information, we may disclose aggregate data about our website’s visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier wants to collect information about you, you will be notified. However, you will never be required to give information to a third party supplier. We restrict the way third party suppliers can use your information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others.

If we sell our website, we may transfer your information to the purchaser of the site. Upon completion of such a transfer, we will no longer possess or control the data received by the purchaser.

Do-Not-Track, Interest-Based Advertising, Remarketing, and Dynamic Ad Serving

Do-Not-Track

We try to honor any Do-Not-Track signals you send through your web browser when visiting our website. However, please read the following important information about “Interest-Based Advertising,” “Remarketing,” and “Dynamic Ad Serving” so that you understand the type of tracking that may be done by third party vendors when you visit our site and how you can opt out of such tracking.

Interest-Based Advertising

When you visit our website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and elsewhere on the Internet about products and services you might like. 

This website does not collect the information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To find out more about Google privacy policies and its DoubleClick DART cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, go to http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/.

Protect My Choices

If you are using Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, or Google Chrome browsers, you may wish to install the “Protect My Choices” browser extensions that are designed to help you protect your opt-out preferences. To learn more, go to http://www.aboutads.info/PMC.

Remarketing

This website may use a remarketing tag to advertise online. This means that Google and other third-party vendors may show our ads to you on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you based upon your past visits to our website.

If you would like to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, you can visit the company’s Ad Preferences Manager at https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.

In the alternative, you can opt out of the use of cookies by third-party vendors by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ . 

Dynamic Ad Serving

Our website may use Google’s Dynamic Ad Serving feature. To opt out of interest-based ads by Google, follow Google’s opt-out instructions located at https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en . 

DoubleClick Remarketing Pixels

Our website may use DoubleClick’s remarketing pixels. If you would like to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, you can visit the DoubleClick opt-out page at https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout. 

Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising.

User Names And Passwords

Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet.

Your Use Of Information And Unsolicited Commercial Email

If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too.

We hate junk email (spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial email or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website’s posting or other communication systems.

Your Voluntary Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties Who Are Not Our Suppliers

You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.

Autoresponders

We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by email. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by sending an email to aj[at]marketingwithyou.com, or sending us mail to the address listed below.

Information Security

We try to keep your information secure. If we become aware of a data vulnerability, where economically feasible, we will attempt to promptly fix it in order to keep your data safe. However, with governments spying online using sophisticated technology and hackers data mining sites, no website owner can guarantee your information will be completely safe from unauthorized access by others. Please take these security risks into account before giving information to us or any other website owner.

Data Retention

We will keep your data for as long as we need it to provide you with products and services, comply with applicable law, resolve any disputes between us or with third parties, and to enforce any contracts between us.

Policy Changes

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website’s home page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us (by email, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes.

If you are concerned about the topic covered by this website privacy policy, you should read it each time before you use our website.

Questions or Concerns

Any questions or concerns about this website privacy policy should be brought to our attention by sending an email to aj[at]marketingwithyou.com and providing us with information relating to your concern.

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:

MarketingWithYou.com Inc

10785 W. Twain Ave., Ste. 102

Las Vegas, Nevada 89135

USA

California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an email to aj[at]marketingwithyou.com or write us at the following address:

MarketingWithYou.com Inc

10785 W. Twain Ave., Ste. 102

Las Vegas, Nevada 89135

USA

This website privacy policy was last updated on October 14, 2015.

Copyright © 2008-2015 Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC and generated with Website Legal Forms Generator software, and licensed for use by the owner of this Website at http://www.marketingwithyou.com. All Rights Reserved. No portion of this document may be copied or used by anyone other than the licensee without the express written permission of the copyright owner. Use of this document does not make the website owner a client of the law firm. Contact the website owner with any questions or concerns about this site.
